all right so I was cleaning my kid's
room and she has a store at the Explorer
buck that she was like to be get rid of
that I hate it's like I hate her she's
her babies okay I need to hate her who
does not like her that's fine but it got
me thinking
but what like why children naturally or
is it naturally like why children start
to hate things that they've outgrown
instead of just being like I think some
of them are probably like me but the
ones that do why it's if you hate no I
want this yeah like why they hate it
like whether it's actually a biological
mechanism so that they and then it also
got me thinking about exes that people
like love someone and then it turns into
hate and I've never really experienced
that I don't kind of angry at someone
but if I love you I love you forever
there's not like it's it's not the same
love but it's love and so I don't know
if I just don't have that peace but I
also and whether it's tied together it's
a good question I have no idea mike says
asking people on facebook about this
exact thing and they are explaining or
saying things so well I want to say
chiming in and that also sounds like
that's anyway they're talking about this
very issue
what ageism and my Dorothy exploring it
and why does the kids hate it but we
also very much a society put into kids
that being a baby is bad that like Oh
babies do that you don't want to do that
some babies do and I remember being a
kid and I really enjoyed certain things
like dolls and I played with them with
my older sister and then I played with
them or like the equivalent with my
younger brother because he wouldn't play
dolls with me so they played like
ours but like they were dolls and then
he outgrew it even though he's younger
than me he all grew that first probably
because I think he didn't like the play
with dolls aspect of it and then but
even my friend group people like my peer
group like I too convinced them in
different ways and I did it fairly
decent job of live but it was like
always a one-off like it was like I had
a big peer group in grade six and like
one person would come over and play with
me with dolls but we wouldn't his school
was like not allowed to be talked about
because we were all too old to play with
them and annoyed they were all at each
other's houses doing that too which is
another weird thing like why we require
kids to grow up in that way like who
cares if I was still playing with dolls
like the whole time I've been like that
we think that's weird but why because
there becomes a point when you do
naturally let them go but if you're
forced to let them go I think you do
hold on to that I don't know doesn't
matter if you learn to the more that
it's just it's why not let everyone grow
into and out of things on their own and
not have attributed to age at all
including a lot of thing like I don't
know would there still be people sucking
on bottles and sue theirs when they were
like 30 if we just left them I don't
know people who absolutely could use the
washroom but didn't because it's also
things that are rather inconvenient as a
parent that you end up using that
language on I don't think I have used
that language but my kid watches a lot
of TV so it's not like she's and
insulated entity if it's only had my
experience on her me teaching her from
on high she's very much a product of the
culture but a conscious product of the
culture too she has me as a parent so
we're constantly talking about
everything that happens and how there
sexism and racism also she's allowed to
enjoy shows so he sounds like like she
doesn't like and that's not true she
loves watch it yeah I don't like watch
it with her but when we watch together
I know I heard as I point out all of
thee all of those type of things
everybody neighbors coming in ageism
remember taking a class about different
kinds of privilege I want different kind
of privileges we have and age is the one
privilege that you start out as in light
like you go from privilege to
non-privileged the other way around not
privileged to privileged and
unprivileged and that is a unique like
we think babies and children are cute
but we are very a dressed towards them
we require them to like act in ways that
they aren't capable of but even more so
than they're not capable of like we're
not capable of and we expect it from
them I mean I do it all the time even
like even though I know I still do it
that's not okay
but it is cuz I'm not capable of doing
that I've been aware of that means I'm
less I can that place as a parent like
you should be able to do this even
though I can't do it why can't you do it
then when I do just let her emerge I'm
in awe and what she does without
learning it for me I never knew it and
she's teaching me it like emotional
intelligence of her own emotional
intelligence uh-huh that distinction
okay it's like her own so like I saw
like I can't name emotions or two in
other people I can't see myself it's
like when it's like what what are you
feeling I don't know why are you asking
that question I'm gonna name this
emotion nope
like good bad anger sad like when they
aren't like that happy a joyful it's
hard to know it's either like they're
not yeah I think they're like not
whatever enough they're not
not whatever enough that's there they
aren't precise enough those sons all
right
they would you come try to come on every
night and just do a five-minute video
maybe people will watch them what house
we'll see good times
join me my work in my room I was
thinking of getting all four Jamis and
just being Jamis on camera like might as
well go with the bright lights little
figure that oh and then I have a reason
to buy pajamas
do you like pajamas that I kind of just
where it's more than I wear my regular
clothes to bed then that I have pajamas
it's like you guys left it I work but
what I wear during the day is pajama
light because it's tights and t-shirts
and the such okay I'm gonna go hang out
with my kid and then